24liveblog.com 2018-12-06

# 24liveblog - Live Blogging Platform, Live Blog Tool, Liveblog Plugin for Wordpress

#### Privacy Policy

##### Last Updated Date: September 19, 2017

We value your privacy as much as we value ours. That's why we at 24liveblog wish to emphasize these underlying principles: 

We make it a point not to ask for personal information that we don't really need, such as your income bracket. 

We won't disclose your personal information to anybody, unless it's for legal purposes, company and/or product development or to safeguard the rights of the company.

It is 24liveblog' policy to respect and keep private any personal information we may collect from you in the course of operating our website.

**Site Registration** For the general public, registration is not necessary to be able to use this website and download our templates for free. But to be able to participate and post in our forum, a registration form should be filled out completely with your desired username, password and email address. Your email address will be used to verify your membership and to contact you about forum related concerns. 24liveblog retains sole ownership of all the information collected on this website. We do not share any personally identifying information with outside third parties.

**Data Security** For security purposes.We process your personal information to: improve and enforce our security measures; combat spam, malware, malicious activities or security risks; and to monitor and verify your identity so that unauthorized users do not access your account with us. We cannot ensure the security of our Services if we do not process your personal information for security purposes.   
Designated Countries: For all purposes listed above, pursuant to the EU General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”) or any equivalent legislation (collectively “Data Protection Laws”), we process the personal information of users located in the European Economic Area (“EEA”), United Kingdom and Switzerland (collectively, the “Designated Countries”) based on our contract with you.

**Legal Disclaimer** 24liveblog reserves the right to disclose your personally identifying information when legally required and when the information is relevant for the protection of our rights, including but not limited to compliance to a legal process or court order served to our website.

**Site User Information** If you are a site member, please be aware that when you share or post personally identifying information, that that information can be seen, stored or utilized by other forum members whom you chose to share the information with. This may result in you receiving unsolicited messages and other forms of communication, depending on the information you shared. 24liveblog will not be responsible for personally identifying information that you share or post in the forum.

**Log Files** Log files contain information that is usually made available by your web browser and is stored on our web server. This non personally identifying information includes the following: browser type, language preference, referring site and the date and time of every page request. Just like most other sites, we collect this information to: have a better understanding of how our visitors use our website, be able to generate reports on the trends relevant to the usage of our website, help with website administration, analyze user activities on the site, and collect information about our user base in general. We do not link the information contained in these log files to personally identifying information and we will never distribute them to outside third parties.

**Cookies and Web Beacons** A cookie is a small text file that a website stores on your computer. This file contains information that your browser provides to the website each time you return. Cookies are used for record keeping purposes. A web beacon is a transparent graphical image that serves to monitor your interaction with a website. This, along with cookies and log files, provides us with analytical information that we can use to improve website performance and user experience in general. We do not link this information to personally identifying information nor do we give this information to outside third parties. This privacy statement regarding the use of cookies and web beacons is only applicable to the 24liveblog website. 

**Third Party Ads** Our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons in the ads that they serve on our website. The use of such technologies will enable the advertiser to store information about your web surfing interests, so that they can show you targeted advertisements that they believe will interest you the most. Our Privacy Policy does not cover the use of cookies and web beacons in the ads of our third party advertisers.

**Managing Cookies** If you do not wish to enable cookies, simply adjust your browser settings before using our website and turn off cookies for 24liveblog or our third party advertisers. Bear in mind, however, that disabling cookies may affect how our site will function for you (e.g. being unable to log in).

**Links to Other Sites** Our website contains links leading to other websites that are not owned or managed by us. Because we are not responsible for how these sites handle your privacy, we encourage you to check out the Privacy Policies of those other websites before giving out your personal information. 

**Changes** 24liveblog reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy as it deems necessary. A notification will be posted on this page, on the homepage of this website, and on other pages deemed appropriate, so that you'll always know what information we collect and what we do with it.
